## Kader Sarıkaya

## Frontend Developer

## Email Linkedin Github Medium

# **Objective:**

I am a design and technology enthusiast, React developer with more than 3 years of experience. I am dedicated to creating seamless user experiences and staying up-todate with the latest front-end development trends. I am excited to join a team where I can learn and grow as a developer.

#### **Education:**

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering, Cukurova University, 2018-2023

Cources: Data Structurs, OOP, Algorithms, Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence

#### **Skills:**

React, Next.js, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, MongoDB, Material UI, Tailwind CSS, Figma, React Native, Three.js, TypeScript, Python-Django

## **Work Experience:**

#### Frontend Developer, Bionluk (Freelance)

January 2023 - Present

- As a Freelance Frontend Developer at Bionluk, I designed unique and userfriendly interfaces using React and Next.js based on client requirements. I also developed my project management skills and gained significant experience in time management.
- Developed and maintained the front-end of the platform using React, Next.js,

### Software Development Intern, Turna.com (Remote)

June 2021 - August 2021

- Worked on developing and maintaining the web application using C#, JavaScript, JQuery, and MsSQL.
- Participated in Agile/Scrum meetings to discuss project progress and prioritize tasks.

## **Hackathons/Bootcamps:**

- Upschool Blockchain developer program with Solana Participated in a 3month bootcamp.
- Won first prize at the UpSchool Solana Blockchain hackathon.
- Participated in the Akbank Refi Hackathon with my university club.
- Currently in a Frontend Developer bootcamp organized by VeriLab

### **Projects:**

Cukurova Block Website - Developed a website for the university club using Next.js,
 Tailwind CSS, TypeScript, Framer Motion, and Sanity. Github | Website

- Recipe Sharing Mobile App: In this project, I developed a mobile application using React Native that focused on recipe sharing among users. The application utilized the MERN (MongoDB, Express.js, React, and Node.js) stack for its backend infrastructure. Github
- Cards of Dragon Developed a game website using React and TypeScript.
  Website | Github
- Figma to React Rebuilt solana ecosystem page according to Figma design <u>Website</u> |
  <u>Github</u>

For more projects, please check out my Github profile!

#### **Articles:**

Context API vs Redux: Which State Management Solution is Right for Your React App?

React Useref and Forwardref Guide by Examples

<u>6 State Mistakes Every Junior React Developer Makes</u>

What Is An NFT? Non-Fungible Tokens Explained

### **Volunteer Activities:**

Led the development team of the Cukurova University Blockchain Club for a semester, organized various events.

## Languages:

English (Fluent)

Turkish (Native)